Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records, 1918-1974 (PPFA I)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series III. PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION OF AMERICA1942-1962
  - Law and Legislation
    - Massachusetts
      - Correspondence and Reports1917-43 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, re: Clinic Closing and Court Procedure1937-1938 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Field Reports1938-1944 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Initiatives Petition Campaign1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Joint Action with Connecticut1941, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Legal Briefs and Documents1938-1942 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Legal Situation1943 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Massachusetts League Raid1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda regarding Birth Control Legal State1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Minutes of Discussion of Massachusetts case1938 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - National Committee for Medical Rights in MA1942 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Publicity1930-1948 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
      - Censorship1929-1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - National Committee for Revision of the Comstock Law1938 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - National Legal Committee (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Social and Legal Status of Contraception literature1930-1948, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 4-8)
    - New York, Petition to Legalize Birth Control1916 (Box 28, Folder 9-11)
    - New York Bill to Legalize Birth Control advice1928 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - State Laws regarding Contraception and Marriage1932-1939 (Box 28)
      - General 1932-1939 (Box 28, Folder 13-16)
      - Report by Hazel Moore1939 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Washington1938 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - U.S. vs. One Package
      - Brief1937 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Documents1930-1938 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Publicity1934-1938 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 72nd Congress 1931-1932
      - Congressional Record1931 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - House Protest1932 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Ways and Means Committee1932 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 73rd Congress1933-1934
      - Catholic Propaganda1933-1934 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Hearing Data1930-1934 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Interviews1933 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Judicial Committees1933-1934 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Judiciary States Campaign1933 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Lobby Reports1933-1934 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Statistics1932-1934 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Tugswell Bill1933-1934 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 74th Congress1935-1937
      - Bills
        - S.15411935 (Box 30, Folder 12)
        - H.R.2000 and S.6001935 (Box 30, Folder 13)
        - H.R.53701935 (Box 30, Folder 14)
        - S.10, S.1375 and S.4000 (Copeland Bills)1935-1936 (Box 30, Folder 15)
        - S.10 (Cutting Bill)1936 (Box 30, Folder 16)
        - S.10, H.R.9495 (Dobbins Bill)1936 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - S.10, Economic Security Act, 113301936 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Congressional Campaign1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - General Data1935-1938 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Judiciary Committee1935 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Legislative Conference1936 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Letters from Surgical Supply House1936 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Lobby Reports1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Petition Campaign1935 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - 74th and 75th Congress1935-1939
      - Legislative Reports1936-1939 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence1935-1939 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Legislation1935-1937 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 75th Congress1937-1939
      - Abstracts1937-1938 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Bills
        - S.10, H.R.5397 (Higgins Bill)1937 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - S.10, H.R.4923 (Geyer Bill)1939 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Legislation1937 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 76th Congress1939-1941
      - Bills
        - S.10, H.R.2281939 (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - S.10, S.1620 (National Health Bill)1939 (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - S.10, H.R.9786, 9917, 1087 (Mead Bills)1940 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Literature
    - Directory of Services1943-1947 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - General1940-1970 (Box 33, Folder 2-5)
    - Infertility1945 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Interpretation to Laymen1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Labor1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Legal Aspects1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Lists of Publications1943-1954 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Marriage Counseling1943-1945 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Medical-General1941-1947 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Medical-Technical1940-1963 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Negro Campaign1942-1966 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Order Forms1951 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Population1940-1960 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Posters/Graphicsn.d. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Public Health1940-1946 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Religious Aspects1936-1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Reprints1936-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - World War II1942-1943 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Printing Production Records (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Support Campaigns with Literature1939-1942 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Literature Catalog
    - General1937-1942 (Box 34, Folder 11-14)
    - Medical/General1941 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
  - Mailings
    - Analysis of Educational Mailings1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Book Mark Mailings, Reports1941-1943 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Clergymen's Follow-up1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Cost of New Mailing1945-1946 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Educational Mailings
      - General 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Heads of Hospitals1943-1945 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Home Economics Teachers1945 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Questionnaire1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Shapers of Public Opinion1945-1946 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Speeches, Etc. for Twentieth-Fifth Annual Meeting Dinner1945 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - State Leagues and Local Committees1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Fortune Reprint Correspondence1943 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Mass Mailings
      - Authors and Screen Writers1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Budgets, Costs, and Estimates1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Editors, Columnists and Commentators1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Labor Leaders1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Plan1943 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Religious Clergyman's Test Mailing1944 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Reports1940-1944 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Reports and Schedules1944-1946 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Social Workers, "The Case Worker and Family Planning," 1943-44 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Syllabus1943 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Medical Department
      - G.P.'s and Sterility Referral Doctors1945 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Medical Department, 500 Referral Doctors1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Lists1942-1947 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Nurses, Techniques of Conception Control1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Presidents and Executive Secretaries of State Leagues1948-1953 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Proposed National Education Group Mailings1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Public Health Doctor's, "Techniques of Conception Control," 1941 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Public Health Mailings1939-1940 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire to Pharmacists1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Referral Physicians1947 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Response Cards1943-1945 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - State and Local Health Educators1946-1947 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - "Techniques of Conception Control," 1938-1942 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - "Techniques of Conception Control," Revisions and Proofs1942 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Policies and Programs
    - Policies1940-1947 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - Program1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Policies, Program1947, 1948, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - International Birth Control Work
      - British West Indies1954 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Brazil1946 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Canada
        - Birth Control Clinic, Toronto1935-1936 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Birth Control Society, Hamilton1935-1936 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Family Planning Association, Calgary, Alberta1941-1945 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Health League1946 (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Marriage Welfare Bureau1943-1945 (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Maternal Health League, Windsor1935 (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Medical Schools1937-1950 (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Parents Information Bureau1933-1945 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - China1924-1948 (Box 39, Folder 11-12)
      - Cuba1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - England
        - General1930-1947, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1-9)
        - British Control Worldwide News Service1937-1937-1940, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 10-12)
        - British Social Hygiene Council1943-1944 (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - The Cecile Booysen Clinic1938-1949 (Box 40, Folder 14)
        - The Eugenics Society1935-1947 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - India1928-1948 (Box 40, Folder 16-19)
      - Japan1935-1950 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Mexico
        - Clinic, Esperanza Oteo 1937-1952 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence
          - Verna Carelton De Millan1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 2)
          - Philip Stoughton1937-1938 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Literature1933-1947 (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - Medical Schools, University of Mexico1942-1944 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Palestine1934 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Poland1957-1959 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Puerto Rico
        - General 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 8-12)
        - Association Pro Salud Maternale e Infantil de Puerto Rico1937-1941 (Box 41, Folder 13-16)
        - Birth Control League of Puerto Rico1932-1934 (Box 41, Folder 17-18)
        - Population Association of Puerto Rico1946-1948 (Box 41, Folder 19-20)
        - Governor J.R. Beverly's Inaugural Address1932 (Box 41, Folder 21)
        - Hospitals1941, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Peru1944-1954 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Philippine Islands1935-1953 (Box 41, Folder 24-27)
    - Marriage counseling
      - 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Pamphlet1942-1944 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Service1930-1947 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Marriage and Family Life1940-1949 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Medical Program, United States Public Health Service
      - Birth Control Program1940-1942 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence
        - Dr. Warren S. Draper1941-1945 (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Dr. Thomas Parren1937-1948 (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Dr. Claude C. Pierce1942 (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - Dr. Leonard A. Sheale1948 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Dr. Mary E. Switzer1942 (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Dr. C. J. Van Slyke1948 (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Dr. R.C. Williams1939-1948 (Box 43, Folder 8-9)
        - Dr. Mark V. Ziegler1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Mailing1938 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Orientation7/7/1944-8/3/1944 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Questionnaire to Department Officers, re: Birth Control1939 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Questionnaires to State and Local Leagues1942 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - State and Local Questionnaire Responses 1942 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - State Depts. of Health, Questionnaire and Assessment1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Minority Groups, Report on Work With1948 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - State Birth Control Work
    - Alabama
      - State Department of Public Health1939-1941 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Suppository Study1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Alaska1928-1944 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, Field Reports (by Mildred Delp)1940-1942 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Arkansas1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - California
      - Correspondence
        - 1941 (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - re: Gifts for M. Delp's Work1939-1941 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Farm Security Administration Project1939-1941 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Field Reports by Mildred Delp1939-1947 (Box 45, Folder 4-7)
    - California and Arizona, Field Report of Miss Delp on Birth Control and ImmigrantsFeb. 1, 1939 - October 1940 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Colorado1938-1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Delaware1932-1944 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Georgia
      - Correspondence with Gov. Ellis Arnoll1944-1946 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Field Reports by Ethel Peters1941-1945 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Health Department Project1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Public Health1938-1942 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Hawaii
      - Palama Settlement and Child Spacing Clinic (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Queens Hospital1938-1952 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Indiana, Correspondence, Public Health1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Kentucky: Public Health1939-1941 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Louisiana (Box 46, Folder 10A)
    - Massachusetts, Conferences, Pamhlets1931 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Mississippi
      - Correspondence1938-1944 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Public Health1941-1946 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nebraska1941 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - New Mexico1938 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - New York
      - Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Hospital dispute over contraceptive counseling1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 4-7)
      - Hospital dispute, "Anatomy of a Victory" 1959 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina1937-1942 (Box 47, Folder 9-11)
    - Oklahoma1943 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Oregon1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - South Carolina1939-1942 (Box 47, Folder 14-16)
    - Tennessee
      - 1934-1950 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Nashville Clinic1940 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Texas1936-1948 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Virginia
      - 1939-1942 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence1941-1942 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - West Virginia1938-1942 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Distribution of Birth Control Clinics and Services, By State1939, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Series IV. PLANNED PARENTHOOD - WORLD POPULATION1961-
  - "Family Planning Programs in the War Against Poverty," 1966 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Literature1963-1966 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous1965-1967 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, Reports1961-1968 (Box 49, Folder 4-8)
  - Population Control1964-1969 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Reprints1963-1969 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Series V. RELATED ORGANIZATIONS
  - Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau (BCCRB)1928-1939
    - General1925-1938, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1-5)
    - BCCRB and ABCL Clinical Research Department Merger
      - General1938 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - "Summarized Factual Report with Analysis and Conclusions to the Joint Committee representing ABCL and the BCCRB, In the Interests of Coordination"1938 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - "Progress Report 1937 and High Lights of 1938"1938 August 1 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Conference on Problems of Contraception1936-1937 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Literature
      - General1937-1939 (Box 50, Folder 10-11)
      - Catalog1937 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Reprints1938 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - National Committee on Federal Legislation for Birth Control1929-1937
    - General1929-1937, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1-7)
    - Address by Julian Huxley1930 October 28 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - American Conference on Birth Control and National Recovery1934 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report1935 October 1-1936 September 30 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Information Sheets1932 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Conference1936 December (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Literature
      - General1932-1938 (Box 51, Folder 13-14)
      - Sample setcirca 1932 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters1931-1936 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - National Committee on Maternal Health1923-1955
    - Administration1934-1944 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meetings1940-1943, July 29, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
    - Bibliography on Contraception1935 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - By-laws and Plans for Proposed Merger with National Research Council1947-1948 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Certificate of Incorporation1930 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Pregnancy1947-1948 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence
      - 1928-1949 (Box 52, Folder 8-11)
      - With Board of Directors1947-1948 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - With Dr. Weed1947 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Disposal of Material1947-1948 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee1940-1946 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Financing1940-1942 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Letterheads1948 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Medical Subcommittee1947-1948 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Meetings1946-1947 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Members1944-1945 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Minutes and Memoranda1943-1949 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets1931; 1932 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - News Releases and Publicity1946-1948 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Personnel1947-1948 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Proceedings, 3rd Annual Conference on Biology of the Spermatozoa1942 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Reorganization1943-1947 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Reports1928-1936, 1940-1944 (Box 54, Folder 2-3)
    - Research, Correspondence and Reports from Wistar Institution of Anatomy and Biology1947 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Research Pamphlet, "Research in Human Reproduction," 1948 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Research Proposals1942-1949 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Special Projects1943-1944 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - National Committee for Planned Parenthood (formerly Citizens Committee for Planned Parenthood) c. 1938-1942
    - Citizens Committee for Planned Parenthood1938 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - National Committee for Planned Parenthood
      - 1940-1942 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Literature1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Reprints1936 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - International Planned Parenthood Federation1952-1962
    - Correspondence1956, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous1957-1964 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - President's Memorandum Series1958-1959 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Sixth International Conference on Planned Parenthood1959 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Third Annual Report1954-1956 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Series VI. CORRESPONDENCE
  - U.S. Government Departments
    - Children's Bureau
      - National Medical Council on Birth Control1930-1941 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Conflict Between CB and PPFA1942-1947 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Farm Security Administration1937-1947 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Federal Security Agency1941-1947 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Individual
    - Alexander, Dr. Walter1948 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Dr. Henry1947 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Arfmann, L.A.1958 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Beardsley, H.T.E., Inc.1938-1946 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Dr. Murray C., Correspondence, Field Reports, Trips1942 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - De Vilbiss, Dr. Lydia Allen1934-1941 (Box 58, Folder 6-9)
    - Dennett, Mary Ware1939-1942 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Dickenson, Dr. Robert Latou
      - 1938-1942 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - 1943-1949 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - 1950 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Birth Control Atlas (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Drawings [originals in oversize] (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Models (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Publications (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Teaching Model #5 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Durant, Will1936 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - East, E.M.1922-1926 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Eastman, Dr. Nicholson J.1939-1944 (Box 60, Folder 2-3)
    - Edwards, Newton1940-1942 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Ellis, Havelock1924-1939 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Elting, Victor1940-1941 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Ely, Joyce, R.N.1937-1939 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Farnham, Dr. Marynia1941-1943 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Fernsworth, Lawrence1941-1942 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Folsom, Joseph K.1943-1946 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Forster, Dr. A.M.1935 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - French, A.N.1934-1935 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Frothingham, Dr. Channing1946-1947 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Fuld, C.B.F. (Mrs. Felix)1940-1943 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Gaines, Colonel Noel1944-1948 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Gamble, Dr. Clarence J.1935-1943 (Box 61, Folder 9-14)
    - Gray, Mr. and Mrs. Philip H., Jr.1939-1943 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Grinker, Dr. Roy R.1945 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Gruening, Ernest1936-1937 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Gunn and Pratt, Voluntary Health Agencies1944-1945 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Gutherie, Mrs. Marietta1934-1942 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Guttmacher, Alan F. 1974 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Hadley, Mr. and Mrs. Morris1937-1949 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Halsted, Dr. Harbeck1940-1942 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Harms, Dr. Ernest1942-1943 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Hepburn, Mrs. Ethel Remington1934-1939 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Hepburn, Mrs. Thomas1940-1951 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Himes, Norman E.1926-1942 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Holden, Dr. Frederick C.1938-1944 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Hood, Dr. R.C.1941 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Janney, Lawrence A.1940 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Jenkins, Dr. Harry H. 1940-1941 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Kellogg, Paul Underwood1941-1942 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Kenin, Dr. Lena1938 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Kennedy, Dr. Foster1938-1939, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Kingsley, Dr. J. Dudley1938-1941 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Klein, Alice C.1942-1943 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Lasker, Mary1941-1946 (Box 63, Folder 1-6)
    - Lewis, Morris1940-1943 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Linton, Margaret1938-1942 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Little, Dr. Clarence Cook1937-1946 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Long, Elizabeth Barstow1942-1947 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Macarthur, General Douglas (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Mack, Dr. Harold1938-1939 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Madden, Willa1943-1946 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Marion, Kitty1930 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Marousek, Phoebe Tucker1945-1946 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Marsh, Mrs. Robert1935-1945 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Mastner, Dr. Eric M.1933-1939 (Box 64, Folder 7-10)
    - Maun, Ora Patten1945-1947 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Maurer, Rose1943-1944 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - May, Elizabeth Eckhardt1942-1947 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - McCaleb, Zoe1938 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - McCord, Dr. James R.1934-1935 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - McDill, Julia Lee (Mrs. John)1935 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - McEwen, Dr. Currier1941-1942 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - McGoogan, Dr. Leon S.1947-1948 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - McWilliams, William J.1935-1949 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Allison Pierce (Mrs. Louis)1937-1940 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Hazel1936-1941 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Morehead, Willie C. (Mrs. Clyde)1938-1942 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Morehead, Willie C. (Mrs. Clyde), Reports1940-1941 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Morrell, Dorthea1939-1944 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Morris, Dr. Woodbridge E.
      - 1938-1943 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Memos1939-1941 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Publications1936-1941 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Publicity1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Reports1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Speeches1939 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Speeches1940 (Box 66, Folder 4a)
    - Mudd, Emily Hartshorne1939-1947 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Mudd, Dr. Stuart1941-1943 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Mumford, Mrs. Martha1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Mumford, Mrs. Martha, Reports1938-1940 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Carl1935-1939 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Nash, Carol1935 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Nekrassova, Dr. Alla1937-1939 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Nimkoff-Myer, Francis1939-1942 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Nixon, Gwinn1935 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Olsen, Edward G.1933 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Otis, Margaret R.1947-1948 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Parker, Dr. Valeria Hopkins1943-1944 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Parlin, Charles C.1940 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Peters, Ethel T.1940-1945 (Box 67, Folder 9-12)
    - Pierce, Dr. Claude C.
      - 1942-1944 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Memos1942-1943 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Reports1942-44 (Box 68, Folder 3-5)
    - Post, Marion H.
      - 1931-1941 (Box 68, Folder 6-7)
      - Letters Concerning Dismissal (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Posten, Mildred O.1942-1943 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Prather, N. Bess1937 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Pratt, Francis Roberta1938-1940 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Reiwer, Jonas1947-1948 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Riley, Louise Elizabeth1940 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Riggin, Dr. Irl Cephos1946 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, Thomas L.1946 (Box 69, Folder 6)